emailys.com 2014-10-08

# Privacy Policy - Emailys

Emailys is committed to protecting the privacy of our clients and web site visitors. Maintaining it fosters confidence, goodwill and stronger relationships. For more information on how Emailys enforces permission email marketing with our clients, please see our Anti-Spam Policy as well as feel free to contact us.   

### Web Site Information Collection

Unless otherwise stated on our Web site, we collect only the domain name and IP address for each visitor to our Web page, the email addresses of those who communicate with us via email, aggregated and user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit and information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information. We also may track browser types to help us understand our visitors' needs related to our Web site design. There is an optional section of our Web site where input forms require your name, phone number, company, and email address.  
We never sell, share or trade any of our customer information with other companies.  
We do, however, reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.  

### Your Email Lists and Databases

Your Email Lists are stored on a secure server. We will not sell, rent, loan or invite external access to your lists, nor will Emailys use your lists for any other reason than customer support and abuse-monitoring purposes. You should stay assured that your data is kept strictly confidential.  

### Tracking Pixels

Emailys includes a "tracking pixel" in most of the HTML email messages sent. A tracking pixel is in fact a small image in the message's content, which is activated when an HTML email is opened via a request for the image on our servers.  
This enables our clients to track the aggregate number of emails opened. The web beacon does not collect any personally identifiable information. Users that do not want to receive email messages with web beacons can choose to receive their emails in text (non-HTML) format.  
We also provide the capability to track when a URL has been clicked inside of an email message sent by our system. We use this functionality to track which links were clicked and in what quantity, as well as to determine the aggregate number of links clicked. This click tracking functionality does not collect any personally identifiable information.  

### Cookies

We use cookies to record session information, such as past activity at the site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site or customize Web page content based on visitors' browser type.  

### Security Technology

Emailys operates in secure environment by using the latest server, database, backup and firewall technologies. All data resides in a tightly controlled, secure data center that prevents unauthorized access and data security. This means that information about the identity and preferences of individual members is never accessible to anyone from the outside.  
However, we cannot guarantee the security of your data while it is being transmitted over the Internet and through servers that are out of our control - that is after you deploy your messages.  

### Notification of Changes

Emailys will notify its members and users via email if we make any changes to our privacy policy. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify about this fact. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner.  
If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, or the home page, and other places we deem appropriate, so that you are aware of what information we collect and how we use it.  
We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our Web site.

* * *

_Last Updated: 2012-11-01 rev. 2_
